

Olivier Daigneault
3D Creator



https://www.behance.net/ olivierdaignea1



oli1999@hotmail.ca







### **Curriculum Vitae**

My career goal is to specialize in the modeling of 3D environments and objects, as well as 3D animation. I'm very versatile in the multimedia field, from Web development to video editing. I enjoy taking on new challenges to improve my knowledge.

#### Skills

#### **3D Modeling**

- · Object and character modeling
- 3D Animation
- 3D Texturing

#### **Web Development**

- Graphic design
- Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Website hosting

#### **Games Development**

- Video game programming
- Creation of particle systems
- Game design

#### Design

- Intuitive user interface
- Improving ergonomics
- Creating attractive experiences

### **Qualities**

- Autonomous
- Versatile
- Hard-working
- Team player

### **Hobbies**

- Video games
- Reading & movies
- Ski
- Cats

## **Software**





















# **Programming languages**











Olivier Daigneault
3D Creator



https://www.behance.net/ olivierdaignea1



oli1999@hotmail.ca







# **School projects**

#### **Board game conception project**

- Create a functional board game concept consistent with the universe
- Develop the visuals and elements needed to run the game
- · Present and organize game tests

#### 2D video game project

- Develop the visual style of the game (environment, Tilemap & objects)
- Create and animate characters for integration into Unity
- Produce particle systems for 2D visuals (Unity)

#### 3D video game project

- Create 3D characters and objects (Blender)
- Create static and animated textures (Substance 3D Designer)
- Produce particle systems for 3D visuals (Unity)

### **Education**

#### **Multimedia integration techniques**

Cégep de Saint-Jérôme (2019 - 2024)

#### Science, computing and mathematics

Collège Lionel-Groulx (2017 - 2019)

# **Work experience**

#### Pemana

#### **Versatile Web Developer**

(10 weeks internship)

June 2023 - August 2023

- Develop multiple websites (Vue3 HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Host sites with a domain name on GitHub Pages
- Produce graphic elements (images & logos)

#### Casteliers

#### **Communications Assistant**

(30 weeks contract)

Sept. 2022 - May 2023

- Manage WordPress websites
- Produce graphics elements and videos editing
- Manage social media and newsletter

#### Atmosphäre

#### **Marketing Assistant**

(10 weeks internship)

June 2022 - August 2022

- 3D animation (3ds Max)
- Create communication tools
- Translate documents